Hey everyone, thanks for listening to
the Grow Your Life podcast. My name is
Jeremiah Kowski and in this podcast I
help coaches, mentors, and trainers
scale their businesses to the next
level. Now, today I want to walk you
through what it takes to go from six to
seven figures and what it takes to go
from zero to six figures. We're going to
talk about that whole process in the two
milestones. I believe often times people
have these goals and they have these
dreams and they want to get there, but
they don't really know what it takes. As
somebody who's been able to build a
sevenf figureure business and has been
able to actually help build multiple 8
figureure businesses over the years, I
know what it takes and I've helped guide
and direct hundreds of people just like
yourself to be able to go through this
process. So, what it takes to go from
six to seven figures. Well, let's back
up a second here. If you're not even
making six figures yet, we'll touch on
that a little bit.
100%. You got to believe that it's
possible for you. You're not going to
make any amount in that level. Unless
you believe that it's possible for you
and then you got to do what a person who
does those things does. Often times we
look at and we say well once I arrive at
that level then I will do what a person
who does that does. And that's the
problem because what you do is you get
the results from who you become and the
actions that you do. And so you actually
have to do what a person does who makes
six figures before you make six figures.
To make seven figures, you have to do
what a millionaire does before you make
seven figures. And that's the part where
it just it just messes with people's
heads because we're so ingrained with a
very specific way of doing things in our
life. There's a very specific way that
we think that we should do stuff, how we
should show up in the world. We have
habits that we are convinced, okay, this
is how I do things. is this and and I
don't want to deviate from this because
well what if my friends what if my
family and and ultimately we literally
let fear and worry stop us from having
the kind of success that we want. Okay.
Now to get to six figures
honestly it's a lot easier than you
think. It's about having value, doing
the work, disciplining yourself to show
up to do the hard things even when you
don't feel like it enough to get people
to pay you six figures. Unfortunately, a
lot of times it has more to do with your
belief in what your value is and being
afraid that people won't see it or that
they'll think you're taking advantage of
them or all this type of stuff that is
preventing you from making six figures.
I've not earned less than six figures
myself
personally
minimum since oh gosh when was the year
when I first the it was like it had to
have been at least 2016 so almost 10
years now I've not earned less than six
figures in fact I haven't earned less
than a quarter million dollar in almost
the last 10 years okay and so take it
from me as somebody who has gone from
being able to earn that to then finally
um earning it and
then you know ups and downs. I earned it
in a job and then I earned it in a
business. It's because I didn't accept
any less than that. And you got to raise
your temperature of what you are willing
to accept as the bare minimum for you to
reach those next levels. And this is
what applies at both levels. For you to
reach six figures and for you to reach
seven figures, you got to get a vision
for where you're going. You got to be
able to see it happen before it happens.
You got to be able to see
clearly it coming to pass for you. You
making six figures and seven
figures before it actually happens. You
got to feel what it would feel like
internally in your nervous
system. You got to start to meditate on
that. You got to start to believe that
it's going to
happen. And I'll tell you, mindset
matters more than anything else. both at
both of these levels. Now, when it comes
from a strategic level, in my wealthy
coach academy program, I coach people
every single day on what to do. What are
those actions to be able to make that
kind of money? Well, as a coach and as a
mentor, you got to get leads on your
email list and then you close those
leads. And that means you're going to
have to talk to people who might not
want to talk to you, but you find who
the gold are. You find the ones who are
willing to talk to you and you turn them
into clients and you don't worry about
what everybody else thinks about you.
You don't stop because you're
concerned with are they going to like
me? Are they going to accept me? Well,
what if they get annoyed with
me? You're not letting that concern
affect you. And that's one of the
biggest things that I noticed prevents
people from making six figures is
they're letting their stinking thinking
stop them from doing that. being
concerned about what other people think
about
them. They're trying so hard to do
everything perfect. They call it a
spirit of excellence. Spirit of
excellence is what keeps people from
making six figures, not what makes it.
That's what I've noticed more than
anything else. And then to get to seven
figures, it's about
systems. It's about optimizing your
time, optimizing your life. And this is
the part that a lot of people won't do
because it's actually very easy to make
six figures, even multiple six figures.
I can make multiple six figures half
halfassing it in my life. But to get to
seven figures, that's where you got to
really double down on the
self-discipline, on the systems, on the
optimization, on the time management, on
the not making excuses, on the not
letting your situations prevent you from
doing something. You know, I have
friends of mine who they have never
earned less than a million dollars in
decades. And it's because they literally
can't think as somebody who would earn
less than a million
dollars. One big thing is they don't
need to do all the work themselves. A
big thing about going to a million
dollars is outsourcing, delegating,
getting other people to do the work for
you, not needing to be the one that does
all the work yourself. and then learning
how to utilize those systems to just do
more, make more offers, and just do more
of what got you to six figures.
Oftentimes, what gets people to seven
figures is just doing more more often
and more leveraged of what got them to
six
figures. So, if you got to six figures,
what if you just talk to more people?
Well, you say, "I don't have enough time
to." Well, okay. Figure out how to hire
a sales team. Train a sales team to talk
to more people for you. Now you've
duplicated yourself. You see what I'm
saying? And that's what it is. And
oftentimes we have the pride and ego
that says, "Well, I got to do it all
myself." And that's what keeps us from
making seven figures is feeling like we
got to do it all ourselves. You got to
leverage your time. And then you want to
connect with more people. If I can
connect with a hundred people this month
and that makes me six figures, to make
seven figures, I got to try to connect
with a thousand people a month. And
that's really sometimes all it is is a
numbers game at that point. And then you
figure out, okay, what systems are well,
I don't have enough time. I don't have
enough energy. I don't have the ability.
I don't make the the finances to be able
to contact that many people, reach that
many people right now. Well, great. What
systems can you put into place? How can
you leverage things to be able to do
that? It's instead of I can't, I can't,
I can't. It's how can
I how can I make it happen? What can I
do? and we stop
complaining. And listen, I get it. Life
happens. One of the biggest things that
happened in my life recently over the
last two years has been the biggest
blessing because it's taught me to
double down on my systems and
optimization. My wife gave birth to two
incredible healthy baby boys and it has
changed our lives. I've had to optimize
my business to be more automated.
Everything in my business is automated
where I don't have to do all the work
myself. I utilize AI. I utilize team
members to get things done faster,
quicker, and on
time. And that's what allows me to work
less hours to be able to create far more
wealth and finances for myself and my
family is to be able to do that. And so
if you want to know what it takes, you
want to just get to six figures. Well,
it's going to take getting over yourself
and actually becoming kind of a
different person in a sense. Becoming
that person who can earn six figures.
You might have to hang out with
different people. I remember actually
changing my friend group of who I was
hanging out with was one of the number
one things that affected my ability to
make that kind of
money. And then going to seven figures
was about doubling down on what it took
to get me to six figures. It was about
getting more serious with my time, not
making as much excuses, changing my
habits, figuring out how to get more
done faster and optimized with less
time. And so that's what really what it
is. And that's that's what it takes.
Often times often times we think that
there's something else going on. Maybe
something else going on is what's going
on between your head, your mental
health, working on your your mindset,
working on how you're thinking about
things. One of the best ways to work on
your mindset. Number one, getting a
therapist. Number two, you can use AI
like chat GPT to actually talk through
problems that you might be having in
your mindset and your thinking. And it
can help you solve those things. Having
a therapist and even working with AI to
be able to help you with your mindset is
one of the greatest things that was able
to unlock the goals, the vision, and the
dreams that I had my life to be able to
figure out, okay, why do I do things the
way that I do? What's going on deeper?
Why do I keep self-sabotaging? This was
one of my biggest things. I would reach
levels where I should be making multiple
millions of dollars, and then I would
sabotage and fall flat on my face and
have to start over again.
Why is that? What was causing me to
sabotage? What was the root of those
things? Getting to the root told me why
the fruit was a certain way. The fruit
is the outcome that I was getting. And
by getting to the root, I was able to
change my behavior, change my habits,
change how I'm showing up. And I can
literally see everything in my life
start to shift as I do that. And it'll
shift for you as well if you do the same
thing. Listen, if you're a coach,
mentor, trainer, I'd love to work with
you. I'd love to help you get to six and
seven figures in my Wealthy Coach
Academy program. I help people every
single week process through, work
through, write their ads, their sales
copy, get more leads, more clients, and
make their business successful. That's
what I can help you with as well in my
Wealthy Coach Academy program. Make sure
you jump in there with us. Jump into one
of the free trainings that we offer.
It's over on my website at
jeremagowski.com.
I'll see you next week. We'll talk soon.
Have a good one.
[Music]
[Applause]